Sex, cinema and punk rock. 1969
Zeroville is a comedy, drama film directed by James Franco.
A young actor arrives in Hollywood in 1969 during a
transitional time in the Industry.
Vikar, played by James Franco.
Soledad Paladin, played by Megan Fox.
Viking Man, played by Seth Rogen.
Zazi, played by Joey King.
Dotty Langer, played by Jacki Weaver.
Montgomery Clift, played by Dave Franco.
Zeroville is a 2019 American comedy-drama film directed by James Franco,
based on the 2007 novel of the same name by Steve Erickson.
The film stars Franco, Megan Fox, Seth Rogen, Joey King,
Danny McBride, Craig Robinson and Jacki Weaver.
The film was first announced in March 2011, but did
not begin filming until October 2014.
Originally set to be released in 2015 or 2016 by Alchemy, the distribution of the
project was held off following the company's filing of Chapter 7 bankruptcy.
It was eventually picked up by myCinema, and was released on September
20, 2019 in limited theaters, to largely negative reviews.
The film was nominated for three Golden Raspberry Awards.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, hollywood, 1960s.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.